<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfDialogue xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Dialogue>
    <lines>
      <string>Greetings noble warrior, welcome to this little piece of hell on the Earth! Looking at the decoration I'm sure you can tell what type of place is this, but just in case let me explain you how everything works.</string>
      <string>To make long story short, there's a bunch of... "not very friendly creatures" around here, so when you see a purple explosion get ready to fight!</string>
      <string>You can use your sword pressing -LEFT CLICK- or -SPACE-, and if you press -SHIFT- you will dash, and your mana bar will decrease.</string>
      <string>The mana bar will regenerate over time, but if you kill an enemy it will gain a bigger amount of mana to once.</string>
      <string>Every time you take damage your health will decrease, so open your eyes when any of those creeps I mentioned appears.</string>
      <string>Whenever you kill one of them your XP bar will fill, and so you will level up eventually. Everytime that happens you can waste your XP points to improve a skill in the Abilities and Missions menu, pressing -TAB-</string>
      <string>There are also be some friendly parners in here, so dont be afraid and talk to them. Some may even give you missions to complete. It's nice to help others you know, so give them a hand!</string>
      <string>I think that's pretty much all you need to know, good luck in your adventure!</string>
    </lines>
    <id>EntranceGuard_S</id>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <lines>
      <string>Thank godness, another adventurer, what a relief! You look pretty strong, would you mind making me a litle favor?</string>
      <string>There's a bunch of creeps around here, and they won't let me escape this darn dungeon... Could you kill five of them?</string>
      <string>With five of those creeps down I might be able to take on the rest of them and go back home at last. Godd luck in your quest my saviour, I'll be waiting here four your return.</string>
    </lines>
    <id>LostWarrior_S</id>
  </Dialogue>
  <Dialogue>
    <lines>
      <string>You actually did it! I mean, not that I didn't have faith in you of course...hehe.</string>
      <string>H-hey, d-did you hear that? It sounded like rocks breaking to pieces. Maybe a blocked path just opened, it happens pretty often in this place.</string>
      <string>Anyway, I can finally leave this place, thank you so much noble warrior!</string>
    </lines>
    <id>LostWarrior_E</id>
  </Dialogue>
</ArrayOfDialogue>